André Luiz da Silva

Software Engineer

jobs@andresilva.cc

% +55 47 99900-1415

andresilva.cc

github.com/andresilva-cc

A software engineer with professional experience in web and mobile applications. Led and participated in the project and development of applications for public and private companies in the most diverse segments, using languages and tools such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js, Nuxt, Drupal, PHP, Laravel, Node.js, and NativeScript. Holds a BS in Computer Science and is constantly improving himself and studying new technologies.

Experience

Front-end Engineering Consultant @ Atlas Technologies

Mar 2022 - Present

- Mentoring and technical guidance to front-end engineers
- Monitoring of squad initiatives
- Study and development of project improvements
- Creating and updating chapter documentation
- Code review

Front-end Engineer @ Atlas Technologies

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022

Assignments in a squad:

- Front-end development for a platform with more than 20 million monthly visits
- Front-end responsible for the deployment process
- Code review
- Tracking and organization of tasks in Jira using Scrum

CEO & Co-Founder @ Nuxstep

Jun 2018 - Oct 2021

- Planning, development and deployment of web and mobile applications
- Participation in the execution of IT infrastructure projects
- Development of a plugin that integrates Spotify's SDK into NativeScript using TypeScript

Software Development Intern @ Gmaes Telecom

Mar 2017 - Dec 2018

- Participation in the development of a web inventory system for the City Hall of Francisco Beltrão using Vue.js and Laravel
- Planning and development of the new website of the Federal Council of Engineering and Agronomy (CONFEA) using Drupal
- Development of an integration between the Nuvemshop e-commerce platform and SkyHub marketplace integrator using Nuxt and Node.js
- Deploy of applications on Linux and Windows servers

Education

UNIVALI - Universidade do Vale do Itajaí

2015 - 2019

Bachelor of Computer Science

Technologies

HTML Express
CSS SQL

Sass NativeScript
JavaScript Flutter
TypeScript Adobe XD
Vue.js Figma
Nuxt Java

Drupal Shell Script
PHP Linux

Laravel Windows Server

Node.js